>> Jem Young: 好的，我们有服务器，我们能用服务器做什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right, we've got our
server, and what can we do with a server?
>> Jem Young: 这是一个窍门问题，我们可以为所欲为。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's a trick question,
we can do whatever we want.
这是我们的计算机，我们可以让它响应我们想要的请求。
This is our computer, we can make it
respond to requests that we want.
我们可以让它响应 ping ，我们可以使它不响应 ping。
We can make it respond to pings,
we can make it not respond to pings.
在接下来的几个小时里
Over the next couple hours more instance,
明天我们会做些更先进的事情
tomorrow we'll do some
more advanced things.
但今天我们要建立一个服务器
But for today,
we're gonna set up a server,
我们会切换用户将使用户具有许可权
we're gonna switch user we're gonna
make that user have permissions to
做我们想在指引内做的事情
do everything that we wanted
to do within guidelines.
但就像我说的我们现在正在路上
But like I said, we're in route now
you can tell by the hash sign and
我想说的是我想说我是谁
the same thing I can clear it out,
so I want to I wanna say who am I?
>> Jem Young: 这是一个真实的问题，我每天在镜子里问自己
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's a real question I asked
myself any day when I look in the mirror I
说我是谁呢
say, who am I, really?
但我是根我们不想成为根
But I'm root and we don't wanna be root,
我们想做别人我想做吉姆你想做你
we wanna be someone else,
I wanna be Jim, you wanna be you.
你想做的不是根
You wanna be something
other than you root,
其实你几乎从来不想做根因为它是为了
in fact you almost never wanna do
things as root because it's to
当有人说你的黑客电脑酷的时候
the fact that when someone says
your hackers computer cool person.
没有人来找我就像我有根
No people come up to me
like I've got root and
这意味着他们可以完全访问您的服务器。
that means that they have
full access to your server.
事实上，它自己的破碎和接触只是我的常规。
In fact, its own broken and
had access is just regular me.
也许他们能做些什么能让他们惹上麻烦
There's probably they could do some
stuff they can cause some trouble but
没那么多
not as much.
但如果他们有根，可以做很多很多坏事。
But if they have root,
they can do lots and lots of bad things.
但在我们这样做之前我想买个域名
But before we do that,
I wanna buy a domain, all right, and
你想让它完全是任择性的
the domain you want it's totally optional.
你不需要买个域，你可能要一个 czz ，我们要成立一个
You don't have to buy a domain, and you
probably want one cuz we're gonna set up
一个子域我们会做很多其他的事情
a subdomain we're gonna do lots
of other things like that.
但是你不需要，你什么都可以用 IP 地址，但是
But you don't actually need to, you can
use an IP address for everything, but
我想买个域因为这是最后一个真正的一步
I wanted to buy a domain because it's
the final step in setting up a real
应用程序，为公司提供真实的 Web 站点。
application, a real website for a company.
我使用 namecheap.com 你可以用你想要的东西
I use namecheap.com,
you can use anything you want,
我们不会对实际的领域供应商做太多的工作
we're not gonna do too much with
the actual domain provider itself.
但是，我使用 Namecheap ，因为托管我的所有域。
But I use Namecheap because that
where all my domains are hosted.
我知道他们的布局，他们的 UI 有点过时了，在我看来，对不起， Namecheap。
That's I know their layout, their UI is a
bit dated, in my opinion, sorry Namecheap.
但是买域你可以用谷歌，你可以用 " 去爸爸" ，
But buy domain you can use Google,
you can use Go Daddy,
你可以用任何你想要的东西
you can use whatever you want.
购买便宜的东西，因为它是您的测试域，或者
Buy something cheap because
it is your test domain, or
买个真正的域名你正在建立一个真正的服务器它是你的全部
buy a real domain cuz you're setting up
a real server, it's wholey up to you.
我要买我能想到的最有趣的域名
I'm gonna buy the funniest domain
name I could think of, and
看看他能不能击败我
we'll see if he can beat me.
所以我要用 Namecheap 没有引荐链接
So I'm gonna use Namecheap,
there's no referral link or
任何类似的内容，都可以使用 Google 或您需要的任何主机。
anything like that, you can use Google or
any hosts you want.
我推荐的是便宜的，很有趣的，但是你做了，所以
I recommend .party cuz it's a cheap
domain and it's funny but you do you, so
如果你买了一个，很多人会坐在他们多年前买的
if you bought a, lot of people will sit
on domains they bought a years ago for
一些他们从来没有得到过的项目
some side project that
they never got around to.
这不是我的工作让你觉得内疚你是个忙碌的人
And it's not my job to make you feel
guilty about that, you're a busy person,
你没时间去探索这些领域
you don't have time to
explore these domains.
但是你可能有个坐在身边的人感觉自己
But, just so you might have had one
sitting around, feel like myself,
我有 20 个领域只是坐在那里
I have like 20 domains that
were just sitting there.
我可以告诉你上一次我带了 jem.party
Well, I can tell you,
last class I brought jem.party,
这很有趣但那是最后一个课我想把它混在一起
which is pretty funny but that was
the last class, I wanna mix it up.
所以我买了 jem 是最好的，jemisththe.最优的，是的，那是一个真实的领域。
So I bought jem is the best,
jemisthe.best, yes, that's a real domain.
我想买个小怪物但它就像 2 万美金的怪物
I tried to buy party.monster, but
it's like $20,000 party.monster.
我希望你能挑选出一些令人难忘的东西
Anyways, hopefully you pick something
memorable and easy to type and
只要你再给我打个字就好了，如果不行，就好了。
nothing too long cuz you will be typing
it quite a bit, if not, it's okay.
您现在就可以使用 IP 地址，就像我们之前说的，域名是
You can just use the IP address for
now like we said earlier, domain name is
只是为了帮你记住因为你没有给你的 IP 地址
just to help you remember that because
you're not given your IP address.
但是我们之前谈到域如何通过名称服务器获取结果，但是
But earlier we talked about how domains
get results via the name servers, but
因为名称服务器保存记录，它们被称为 DNS 记录。
the results because the name servers keep
records, and they're called DNS records.
还有不同类型的 DNS 记录取决于您想做什么。
And there's different types of DNS
records depending on what you wanna do.
大多数记录称为 A 记录，它们将名称映射到 IP 地址。
Most records are called A records,
and they map a name to an IP address.
例如， jemoung.com 映射到23.不管点，工作，看，我不
For instance, jemoung.com maps to
23.whatever dot, that works, see, I don't
记得我自己的 IP 地址，我已经有了七年了，所以我不记得了。
remember my own IP address, I've had it
for like seven years, so I don't remember.
您想知道的其他记录是 CNAME，并且仅映射 A 或
The other record you wanna know about is
the CNAME, and that just maps an A or
与 IP 地址不同名称的规范名称。
an a canonical name to a different
name versus an IP address.
例如， jemyoug.com 是 A 记录，因此
For example, jemyoug.com is a A record, so
将 jemyoug.com 映射至 23.23.185.61
it maps jemyoug.com to 23.23.185.61
与 blog.jemyoug.com 是 CNAME 记录。
versus blog.jemyoug.com,
that is a CNAME record.
因为它将子域映射到 IP 地址，
Because it maps the sub
domain to an IP address,
它将它映射到 jemyoug.com 然后将它映射到 23.23。
it actually maps it to jemyoug.com and
then that maps it to 23.23.
我们这样做的方式
And the way we can do this,
我们可以检查给定域是否有使用 dig 命令的记录。
we can check on the records that a given
domain has is we use the dig command.
所以我们去尝试一下，你可以在你的服务器上使用它。
So let's go and try that out,
you can use it on your server or not.
我要退出我的服务器我不喜欢用根做事情
I'm gonna exit my server cuz I
don't like doing things with root,
你永远不知道
you just never know.
所以我要退出然后继续挖我说在 jemyoung.com上
So I'm gonna exit and run dig, and
I'll say run dig on jemyoung.com,
我们会知道我们有什么记录
we'll see what kinda records we have.
>> Jem Young: 有什么意思吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Anything interesting?
是啊现在我们只有一个我们有个 A 记录
Yeah, so right now we just have one,
we have an A record,
我们之前说过的就是这个 IP 地址
which we talked about earlier and
that's this IP address.
您可以在大多数域上运行挖掘
And you can run dig on most domains and
就能挖掘出它拥有记录的记录
it's just gonna dig up what sort of
records it has who holds records,
就像拥有这个电话簿的人
essentially like who owns this
phone book that maps this to this.
但如果我说挖的话我会说 blog.jemyoung.com
But if I say dig,
I'll say blog.jemyoung.com,
它是一个子域， >> Jem Young: 它给我 2个。
which is a sub domain,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It gives me a 2.
它给我一个 CNAME ，它重定向 jemyoung.com
It gives me a CNAME,
which redirects jemyoung.com, and
然后它会给我一个映射到实际 IP的记录。
then it gives me the A record
which maps to the actual IP.
所以我们看到 CNAME，只是映射到另一个域，
So we see the CNAME,
just maps to a different domain, and
然后在内部映射到 A 记录。
then internally that maps to an A record.
我知道你是这样我为什么要在乎
I know you're like, why should I care?
你在乎的是我们马上要把它设置好
Well you care because we're
about to set it up right now,
我想让你知道你在做什么我也不是在自说自话
and I want you to know what you're doing,
and I'm not just self telling you things.
但那是挖出来的所以你可以说
But again that was dig,
so you can say man dig,
它有实用，很直接。
it has the utility,
pretty straightforward.
想知道谁有我们网站的信息就好了
Its good if you wanna know who has
information about our website things
就像这样
like that.